slicingupeyeballs.com 2019-05-09

# Privacy Policy - slicing up eyeballs // 80s alternative music, college rock, indie

At **Slicing Up Eyeballs,** the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that are received and collected by **slicingupeyeballs.com** and how that information is used.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by e-mail at [info@slicingupeyeballs.com](mailto:info@slicingupeyeballs.com).

###### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, **slicingupeyeballs.com** makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement around the site and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information, are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

###### Personal Information

**slicingupeyeballs.com** may collect personal information in the form of names and e-mail addresses, or other voluntarily provided information, when readers leave comments on the site or enter the site’s periodic contests. **slicingupeyeballs.com** does not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties personally identifiable information. However, **slicingupeyeballs.com** reserves the right to release personal information when such a release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce site policies or protect the site’s or others’ rights, property or safety.

###### Cookies and Web Beacons

**slicingupeyeballs.com** does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that visitors send via their browser.

###### DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on **slicingupeyeballs.com.**
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to **slicingupeyeballs.com** and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Google Privacy").

###### Advertising Partners

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.

Our advertising partners include:

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in the advertisements and links that appear on **slicingupeyeballs.com** sent directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript or web beacons) may also be used by third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

**slicingupeyeballs.com** has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. **slicingupeyeballs.com’s** privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or Web sites.

###### Disabling Cookies

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific Web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective Web sites.
